Here we go!
I'm going to do a joint bandaids now!
I want to eat beef tongue once!
Let's eat beef tongue once!
I want to eat beef tongue.
Oh, you mean...?
Do you want to split into two teams?
We're divided into two teams.
I'm the only one.
He wants beef tongue, too.
Oh, I want some beef tongue.
What are you going to do now?
We're having a beef tongue dish.
No, no, no.
Bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam bam
You're on the Bum-Bum team.
Which one looks more like...
The bum team or the beef tandoori?
So it's okay then?
Beef Tongue Dish.
I'm going to go stand in line with the bandits now.
Bang Bang Goren.
There's a lot of families here.
Real tag.
Look, it's a real game of tag.
They're filming youtube.
There's a family.
Custom love and Orizou's cute
Hello, there.
How long is the wait?
45 minutes.
I'm super antsy.
Good afternoon.
Today is the day I can't stop sneezing at all!
Woof! Woof!
I can't stop sneezing
I rode it the other day.
I did?
That was fun!
You can see us in the back.
You can see the yellow and pink bars in the back.
As a boa, I got to ride the pink one.
It was pretty scary and noisy.
Zzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz
I'm 35 years old.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
That's what I was yelling at the top of my lungs!
From now on we were
We were going up to the bandit.
But it was too crowded and we couldn't get on.
We are going to the Hashihiro.
The other members of the group
The other members are buying different kinds of beef rolls.
Okay, Yuna, come in.
Good afternoon.
I'm Yuna Nakamura
I'm Yuna Nakamura.
Attendance number 17, Yuna Nakamura.
It's hard to say, isn't it?
I'm Yuna Yuna.
Oh?
Lucky you.
So, from now on...
I'd like to board the Hashihiro.
Let's see who it is.
I'm going on the Hashiguro.
It's so hot right now.
Um...
Oh! This way.
This way.
Very much.
Um...
The amusement park itself is crowded.
Certainly today.
All from 30 minutes to
Up to 40 minutes
Waiting time.
The Hashihiro
This was a lot of fun.
The buffet itself is
I'm a little scared of the buffet alone.
I'm a little scared.
but it's a little scary when it's just a buffet.
Hashihiro-go is going around
while the Viking is going around.
so it doesn't feel fluffy at all.
It's just a lot of fun
It's very fun to see the air
It's a very fun playground equipment!
I don't know how long we'll have to wait.
But that car...
You can only go in one at a time.
I think we can make it.
Yeah!
Let's go!
We're in between the first and second
Because we are in an amusement park
we have a time limit
about 30 minutes.
I'd like to play after we're done.
I'd like to ride the Hashihiro
Yes, ma'am.
I ate some fries.
I think I have something on my lips.
Salt.
If you look closely...
If you look closely, you can see it.
I don't know how to cut it off like this.
If I cut it, will it stop?
I'll stop it.
What?
Can you confirm that it's the right one?
Prove it.
I wanted to ride with you.
I'm assuming you can't dance and ride, but I got bullied. I'll see you later.
I wonder if it's in there now... but it might be dangerous...
I'm more nervous about being a packager than a barge runner.
I'm not going to show you either.
Yuna, it's okay... we'll make it.
You've got it, you've got it, you've got it
If it were me, I'd be holding it right there.
It's not even 30 centimeters long.
It's not even 30 centimeters in.
Right here.
Wow, we rode that one.
We rode this one.
It wasn't that fast.
I think you did great.
Oh no!
Now we're going to ride the Hashbirgh!
I'm so excited!
I couldn't ride here, because...
Yes, I used to not be able to ride.
I want to show you how much I've grown.
Can you handle it, Mi-chan?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Because I'm the only one here with an anime.
That's amazing.
What do you always do when you're in line?
I'm always so nervous.
I know.
I believe in God.
Who can wait for Staker?
I can wait. I can wait.
You're the one who can't wait.
Impatient.
Who can wait for Staker?
Oh, you're not on a cell phone.
Go-pro station.
I think I'll get on YUNO or something next.
That's for sure.
YUNOs next?
YUNOs ride next.
I'll be on it in a heartbeat.
Time... in the chest...
Heart throb
Time to get it in the chest
When the chest? I'm scared
Too close? Too close?
I'm not afraid.
Too close?
When I'm nervous
Mockingjay.
You're so cute.
Scary.
Mockingjay
Mocking
Ouch!
Oh, what should I do?
Mie-chan will take a picture
Dakudaki
Breathless!
I'm so excited!
Annyan!
Anyan, you seem mature today.
Anyan, something like ....
I told Mr. Bakumeki that I like his hair! I told him!
And by the way...
What's up?
Hello, forehead.
Hello. - Hello.
Very nice.
Bodeko, you're glowing.
Nice to meet you! I'm Bodeko!
No, it's not my forehead.
I like it a lot.
Well, let me see it.
What?
I could have tightened this, but I'm not stupid.
Trouble.
You're supposed to change it.
Trouble jacket.
Trouble jacket... 2,000 yen in Korea.
What's that?
My portal coordinate for today.
Super cheap!
Please introduce me.
I want to open it.
Open it.
I'm just gonna put it down.
It won't open?
It's such a nice fabric.
It's warm.
But it won't open?
It won't open.
There you go.
I'm on a 2,000-yen budget.
It was on sale for 2,000 yen.
Oh, no, this one didn't open.
I'm supposed to open it, but I'm not.
You mean you can't take it off?
I see.
Wow!
You can call me "Chuck God" from now on.
Chuckman.
I'm Chuckman.
This is
This T-shirt
We're selling it for 3,300 yen.
Ebichu T-shirt
While I'm introducing our products...
Yunopen, Yuno!
Mamoka-chan, Yuno-chan!
You are tall enough!
I'm happy for sure!
I'm always telling him
Yuno is always telling me that I'm doing the choreography wrong.
I have to get angry with him.
It's all backwards.
He's not serious.
I'm so serious.
He's not serious at all.
That's part of it.
I'm more serious.
Why the perfume?
I'm the one who went to match it, and now I have to say, "I'll buy a new one.
I'm supposed to say, "I'll buy a new one.
I'm the one.
But...
I thought I've smelled that scent before.
I thought it smelled good.
It's Yuno.
We use the same perfume.
Well, that's the kind of relationship we have.
That's the kind of relationship.
I don't get it at all.
They use the same perfume.
That's the kind of relationship.
Between you and Momoka...
I have a relationship with Momoka-chan...
What's with you and Momoka?
She doesn't like it. I don't have to tell her. I don't have to leave her.
She doesn't hate me.
She's so happy. The way she opened her mouth.
It's coming right out.
Joyful.
That's a "y" for joy.
You're lowering your voice.
She's happy.
It's hard to see this in her face, but...
Actually, this cute joy.
Only her front teeth are showing.
It's a little longer than usual.
She's so happy!
Let's go!
What's the time?
I think we're done.
Seventeen minutes.
They scared the shit out of me.
Thirteen minutes.
That's close.
Close. Yuna.
So close.
We're done.
Denied.
Three minutes. POETRY
I'm back.
Oh, business.
I'll take your picture.
I went to take a picture.
I went to take pictures.
I'm going to take a picture.
I'm going to take a picture
I'm going to take a picture in front of that word
Like goodbye
Cutang shoe
Please.
After lots of pirates and zero lee sets.
And pirates and setters, you're in for a treat.
Since it will be easier to install
somewhere even if you try to get fucked with a pirate.
We might be able to help you.
We are still waiting for your participation
We are still waiting for you to join us at the feast of the TV related to the event.
It will be on a social networking site somewhere.
This is a lot of letters.
They are letters, aren't they?
Good job!
Hiting.
Yes, sir.
I can push the shutter button, sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I can only press the shutter button.
About the shutter.
I'll say "yes" all the way.
Yes. Cheese.
I'll take another one.
Yes, cheese.
Thank you very much.
Three shots?
Three shots. Shall we do three shots?
Two shots.
Okay, I'll do it.
There you go.
That's it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Okay, here we go.
Vertical.
I'll go for the side too.
Please do it.
Yes, yes, thank you very much.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Thank you very much.
And there's a cherry blossom somewhere.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
There are cherry blossoms.
Well then, I'm satisfied, satisfied.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
At this moment